He's got his hands behind his back.
Oh!
Both of them.
Beautiful!
So cute!
Oh, man! Oh, man!
I'm so happy!
I think I'm the happiest I've ever been in the Corps.
What's this?
Today we are in Akita Prefecture!
Welcome on your first day!
We're here to see you!
Yes!
And today
I'm here at my favorite ranch in Akita!
A ranch!
Yes! It's a ranch!
Yay!
Are there animals there?
I heard there will be animals and you can eat them.
Let's have fun!
I'm off!
Hmmm...
Hmm...
Ponies.
It's in the pony.
Come inside.
Give him this.
Rumor has it that I'm quitting.
Oh, my God! We have to go here and do it!
We have to go here and do it!
You'll see!
Don't stick your hand in your mouth too much.
You're gonna get a refill.
Ah! It's Camellia japonica and Camellia japonica!
Camellia and Camellia!
Ryuhou and Camellia!
Please stop it! It's okay!
It's true!
Don't put it down! Don't put it down!
Stroke his nose! Stroke the white one, too!
Deploy the back!
Peel it off!
Cute!
So cute!
Can I pet it?
Nibble on it!
So cute!
Mr. Tsuboki!
Turn around gently!
I'm going to pet it!
Can we all pet it?
So cute! He's so cute!
Ryuho has a human face!
He keeps turning away!
I feel like I'm getting to know Mr. Ryuho!
I want to touch Mr. Tsuboki!
Excuse me.
Beautiful!
I'm so happy!
Sorry, two shots of a white horse and light.
I think I'll put a horn on it to make it a unicorn.
I agree! I agree!
I was angry.
Let's get to know the shampoo table tenteleble.
I don't know, maybe there's some kind of hierarchy here.
That's a strong "yes".
You have beautiful eyes.
Long neck! Wavy crotch
Thin neck.
Her mouth is so goat-like!
It's a goat!
Goat's movement is a goat
Cute goat.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Goat. I like goats.
A goat. I like goats.
You want a goat?
Oh, my God.
It's so flexible.
It's so soft.Very soft.
Oh, it's Lun-chan.
Bunny.
Thank you.
You're so cute.
He's cute.
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at this.
You like it?
What? The whole time. Look at this.
There's two girls facing each other.
There's a boy and a girl facing each other right there.
I got some allowance, so I'm going to give you a carrot.
Yay!
He's so cute!
Stay here. I'm not letting you in.
Of course you can.
This place is important though.
Wait a minute. Okay, here you go.
Grab a carrot and come over here by yourself.
I'll do it if you rustle.
Oh, here it comes. Here it comes.
Oh, here it comes, here it comes, here it comes.
Good morning.
That's great.
Wow, this is great.
This is, uh, a little scary, isn't it?
It's a little scary, isn't it?
Let's go home.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, my God, sweetheart.
Excuse me, sir.
Oh, they think you're a carrot because you're in my house.
Mm-hmm.
You should go when you get home.
When you get home.
Oh, I'm home.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, they think I'm a carrot.
I don't know what to do.
Oh, they think I'm a carrot.
You're so cute.
You're cute.
I'll give it to you.
I'll give it to you in a minute.
I want it.
It's cute.
Oh, my God.
You're so cynical.
Your clothes are too long.
Watch your back.
Hey, Closer.
Wait a minute.
She's cute.
She's really cute.
You're so cute.
You're cute.
Did you get the last one? Make up a story.
Oh, my God, he's mad at me.
Look! Oh, no, no, no, no.
Look from behind.
It's so cute!
I'll give it to you, it's cute.
Wait a minute.
I was about to give it to you.
Can I stroke it?
You can stroke it.
I was just about to give it to him.
Why would you say that?
What's wrong?
Hey, Blacky.
So cute!
They're so cute.
Too cute.
Look at them.
I want to take a picture from here.
Can I take a picture?
No, it's okay. It's private.
So many white ones!
This is Maeda-Maeda.
Miyanon is cute!
I like her.
She's cute.It's so cute!
I love it.
He's cute.
I love you too.
That black girl...
I love you, too.
I'm right behind you.
Me, too.
Oh, he's suddenly gone.
Suddenly it got away.
Black.
It's hard.
So precious.
That's the most precious video I've ever seen.
It's the most precious video ever.
Oh, sorry.
This bunny is so fluffy!
Fluffy, fluffy, fluffy.
Well, I'd better get going.
You know... you've been right next to me the whole time.
Thank you so much.
I love you so much.
Litter, litter, litter.
I'll stay with your toys.
You'll always be with me, mabutatsuchi.
Thank you so much!
Thank you, Herb.
Here's one for the goat.
Thank you very much.
For the goat.
The manager with the money.
Can I give some to the goat?
Sure.
Carrots.
Can I give them to the goats?
Are you sure?
It says so.
He wants me to have a carrot, too.
So I guess it was a girl.
For me, too.
I'm so happy.
I think I'm the happiest I've ever been in the Corps.
I know.
It doesn't happen very often, does it?
It's like this.
That's amazing.
You're...
You're beautiful.
Oh, my God.
I was laughing so hard.
You could be in show business.
Why don't you join us?
I'm with Starrus Promotions. It's fun.
Would you like to join us?
Snap, snap, snap, snap!
You're scaring me.
Hey, you!
You.
You're scaring me.
I'm a little scared.
Scary.
I'm scared.
I'm not mad.
It's three for one.
Who is it?
I'm looking forward to working with you
Nice to meet you, sir.
Nice to meet you.
Yay!
We're tied!
Hurry up and give it to him.
He can't reach it.
He's being mean.
Let's all dance a little
The sky is white tylenose
Fly, fly, fly, fly
The sky is shining so bright
Fly, fly, fly, fly right in front of me
Fly, fly, fly, fly
The sky is so exciting
Fly, fly, fly, fly in front of my eyes
Go, go, go, go
The sky that thrills meFluttering through the sky
Fly, fly, fly, fly right before my eyes
Go, go, go, go
Fly on and on and on and on
Go, go, go, go, go, go
Go, go, go, go, go
I want some water or something to drink.
What's going on?
I want to go around with you.
Shall we go around?
Let's go around.
Yes, yes, yes.
You don't want to go around?
What's the matter?
Can't you turn?
It won't turn.
Will it turn?
It's water!
It's an idol.
I had a really good time.
Next time we're going for soft ice cream.
Is that okay?
Yeah, let's go.
I'll see you soon.
I'll be back.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Take care of yourself.
Take really good care of yourself.
Let's go on a trip to a hot spring next time.
I'll be back.
I'll see you soon.
Bye bye.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'll be right back.
That's a yellow card.
If you do it again, you'll get in trouble.
I got the money.
Thank you.
Okay, so now I would like to do, um, a cow-squeezing experience.
It's something I've wanted to do my whole life, so it's not a real cow, but I'm going to do it on my practice day.
Good luck!
I'm going!
What?
Ha-ha-ha!
That's hard!
This way? This way?
This way?
Tight with your thumb and forefinger.
Ah! Aah! That's great!
That's great!
Aah! Oh, my God!
Oh, great, great, great!
This is gonna take a lot of power!
Oh, man!
Whoo-hoo!
Thank you.
That's all for now.
That's all.
Yay!
I'm going to go buy some milk now.
I'm going to pick out some milk.
There are so many!
I wonder what's good.
Maybe this one.
A sea of happiness.
Coffee milk? Roselle?
Roselle?
Sounds delicious.
There's so many of them.
They're so cute.
It's so cute.
Milk of happiness.
They sell it there, too.
Which one? Which one?
That's a good one.
You want a chain? Yeah, let's do this one.
Okay, let's do this one.
I'll have this Jersey milk.
Here you go.
There's a lot of it.
Is there this much?
Cafe au lait.
This place is nice.
It's nice. It's really nice.
That was so much fun.
This is a good place for a date.This place is good for a date.
It's really nice.
This is how we can tell people about the charms of Tohoku.
I'm happy if it's getting through to everyone!
Oh my God, that was helpful!
Come on, get into it!
The screen is shaking.
I'm getting drunk.
I don't want to... I don't want to...
I hate it.
I don't like it.
No.
This is scary.
This is awesome.
Oh, here it comes.
Thank you very much.
It's warm.
Here's your milk.
Yay!
Ta-da!
A minuet.
Pot and ice cream.
What's up, ice cream?
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
We're waiting.
There's a place that sells a product called "I love hamburgers.
Oh, how cute!
I love hamburgers.
Oh, it's so true!
That's what I'm talking about.
Yes!
They gave us a meal as a service!
Thank you so much!
You are so kind!
I heard that if I don't eat it soon, it will go belly up...
And cheese toast!
This is the senior who appeared on TV!
He has appeared on TV! He is a senior in the industry!
I heard that Icoma-chan said it's the best in the world!
I'm so excited!
Shall we eat?
Let's eat!
Milk first.
Okay, then.
I'm bored.
Cheers!
Bon appétit.
Oh, it's good.
Delicious, warm
Delicious.
Wow, I feel like I'm growing.
Oh, I'm growing taller.
It's so good!
Thank you, cow.
Thank you. Thank you.
That's really, really easy to drink.
We'd like to try it hot.
It warms you up.
It's so warming.
Iced.
It's so good!
It's really better than water, better than water
Tastes better than water.
It's delicious.
You want some then?
I want some.
I got this one. It's a little runny, so I got this one.
Bon appétit.
Looks good.
Mmm〜〜〜〜〜
Mouth
〜〜〜〜
Hello?
Nothing from me.
Okay, well, thanks for the food.
Happy New Year!
Bon appétit!
This looks really good.
It smells really good.
I heard a good sound.
Mmmmmm
Yummy!
Yummy!Delicious!
Crispy!
Well seasoned!
Great cooking!
Mun-chan no Nako
It's funny when you go to a restaurant and say the food is good!
Because it is, isn't it?
The food is good!
It's got black pepper on it!
It's spicy!
It's kind of spicy and delicious.
It's juicy inside.
It's so flavorful and so good!
Oh my God!
You can only eat it here!
So everyone should definitely come here!
It's absolutely delicious!
It goes really well with milk!
It's the best!
We drank a lot of milk, too.
It's delicious!
Oh, it's absolutely delicious!
Wow!
Are you okay?
Just like that.
Yes!
It smells a little bit.
Oh, it's so cheesy!
Oh, it looks so good!
Oh, man!
Oh!
Oh, yeah!
Wow!
Bon appétit!
Oh, my gosh!
Bread is delicious!
Wow.
The bread is crispy but kind of fluffy.
The crunchy cheese is also very rich!
It's so good!
It goes so well with this bread!
This is really good!
But I'm not being overzealous.
It's really good!
Can I have some, Sei-chan?
Yeah, sure.
I want some!
Everyone can eat this!
This set is great!
I recommend this set.
And milk.
It goes so well with milk!
This is bad!
It goes well with milk, doesn't it?
This is bad.
Quiche N'bois set.
Isn't it really good?
Yes, it is.
Why?
I've been eating it all day.
You've been eating it all day.
Did you hear that? Did you hear that?
That's really funny.
They were eating the whole time.
He's cute.
Did you hear that?
It's cute.
He wants to use it one time in Prince.
I want to use it. You can use it.
I want to keep eating.
I want to eat it all the time.
Cute.
This goes well with it.
It looks like a gravy hand.
Gravy hand?
Coffee.
Blessed, isn't it?
Here it is.
The original Jersey soft!
Wow!
This is also a service.
Yay!
You're so kind
Thank you, Mikan!
Thank you, Mr. Bug!
Thank you
Lose heartLose heart
Bon appétit.
Mmm? Delicious!
So mild.
Delicious!
All at once, you're enveloped in milk.
Oh, I know. Milk
Milk.
It's not like he's forcing himself to say it nicely.
It's like he's really trying to be nice.
I mean Ruki.
I really want you guys to come.
Please.
Please, I want you to meet Mr. Goat.
I'm sure he likes you all.
I'm sure he likes us. I'm sure he likes us.
We'll give him our best shot.
Ask her if she's an office girl or a female.
Yeah, sure.
I don't know.
I'm thinking office.
And then the meth guy turns it.
That looks like a female.
It looks like a female?
Are you sure?
Are you serious?
There are girls like that.
She's the most popular girl in town.
No, seriously.
I'm serious. They're gonna love you.
She's gonna be a hit.
If she can cook and stuff...
She's got a big gap between you and them.
Isn't that amazing?
If she could cook or something, I'd be a big fan.
Ninjing Latte
So, we received a lot of food,
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the food.
The sausages tasted really good too.
The pork chops were really spicy and tasty.
It was really delicious.
The soft ice cream was fluffy and tasty,
The milk was rich and delicious.
I was so happy.
I hope you all try it.
I want you to try it.
I hope you go in and eat it,
Take a picture of it and go home.
I recommend it.
Autumn is the best season.
Good for families.
Good for dates.
Good for one person.
Alone is fine too.
Because there is a goat.
I'm not alone.
Akita is the best.
Thank you, Yuka.
Thank you, Yuka-san.
I hope the goat-san has also been able to convey the charm of Akita through this video.
Please come visit Tsuchida Farm, goat-san.
Please come.
Bye bye.